Mills
This way.
Deepali.
Is it male or female?
Ma'am, It's a male.
Sir.
Yes. Yes, sir.
It's a skeleton. Male.
Yes, Sir. The forensic team is here.
Even the media is.
-Silence!
-Ma'am! Ma'am!
You know how it is.
They reach before the police.
Yes, Sir.
Have you found anything, Ma’am?
-Anything odd?
-Yes.
Indeed there is.
A maniac who goes around
giving sermons on dignity
breaks into a closed textile mill
and finds a skeleton
in the dyeing shed.
That is odd.
Of all the police in the city
he calls only me.
That is odd.
The media arrives here
along with the police.
That is odd.
How much more self publicity
you want, Yug Arya?
I did not call the media here.
One of your poli..
Inspector Yug Arya,
I'm at Panchachulli textile mills.
The one you had told me about.
In the dyeing shed, near the bleaching tank
I've found Raghav Nautiyal's dead body.
Nautiyal from the Aditi
Tiwari kidnapping case.
I've a request, Ma'am.
Even that is odd too.
I want the skeleton's DNA
to be matched.
With whom?
With Raghav Nautiyal.
Raghav Nautiyal from the
Aditi Tiwari murder case?
Yes, Ma'am.
Dubka!
Happy Diwali !
My cutie pie, my sweetie!
What happened, Dubka!
Stay here, just be here.
Hello?
Hello, Mr. Anthwal. Hello?
Mr. Anthwal, Yug Arya here.
Mr. Anthwal?
Hello, AnthwalMr. Anthwal?
Hello, Mr. Anthwal?
Can you hear me?
Mr. Anthwal?
Mr. Anthwal. I had some questions for you
How did you come to know
about Raghav Nautiyal's body?
And you said body
but I found skeleton?
You were the one working
on Aditi Tiwari's case, right? Mr. Anthwal?
And which is your police station?
Police Station.
Mr. Anthwal?
Inspector Yug Arya
This is my last transmission.
But it’s not over as yet.
These transmissions will restart in 1990.
But then,
You will have to
remind me of our
transmissions yet again.
No matter what I say then,
don’t give up.
The past can be changed, Inspector Yug.
Whatare you saying?
Just don’t give up.
I don't quite understand
what you're saying.
Mr. Anthwal, Hello I don't understand
what you're trying to say.
Hello?
Mr. Anthwal what happened? Hello!
Hello, Mr. Anthwal?
Revoke the statute of limitations!
Fulfill our demands!
34 Hours
You drove me crazy by
calling me all night long.
I've told you a dozen times.
Currently, there are four Inspector Anthwals
working for the Uttarakhand Police.
And none of them is
associated with the Aditi Tiwari case.
Ram Singh, I wasn't talking to a ghost.
I actually had this conversation, bro.
Then you should've asked him
where he's posted.
It would have made my life easy.
What else?
-We were the UP Police before 2000.
-I see.
- All the records before that are in Lucknow.
- Okay.
Around 15 Inspector Anthwals have
worked with Uttarakhand Police after 2000.
I pulled up this file for you.
All their records are in here.
-15?
-Go through them and find your Anthwal.
Lab
Ma'am.
Vamika.
No point breathing down my neck.
You won't get the reports sooner.
And you can't barge
into the lab so often.
Sorry Ma'am, but this one's urgent.
All the cases here are urgent.
I'll call you when I'm done.
Inspector Yug Arya, please respond.
From the voice, it sounds like.
someone under age 60. 101 percent.
Let’s start with getting
rid of these retired inspectors.
With the retired ones out
I'm left with nine.
These are the ones still in service.
Ram Singh said they
did not handle the case.
So let's delete these as well.
That leaves me with five.
Utsav, Madan, Shaurya, Yogesh
and Vinod Anthwal.
Yes.
His age must be 21 or 22 years.
Do you see this metallic
tip on the shoulder?
This means someone stabbed
him here with violent force.
With a hypodermic needle.
The syringe penetrated
till the bone and the tip broke.
Hello
Who is speaking?
-Inspector Anthwal?
-Yes, what is it?
This is Yug Arya.
Yug Arya, who?
You spoke to me on the
walkie-talkie yesterday.
You creditors don't back off.
Do you know what was found on the tip?
Etomidate.
It is a short acting anesthetic agent.
It is normally used in hospitals
to instantly anesthetize patients
with brain injury.
This indicates someone injected
and rendered him unconscious first
after which he was injected
with an overdose of
a semi-synthetic adulterated form of heroin.
We've found traces of this
heroin on the aluminum foil and syringe..
recovered from the crime scene.
Any fingerprints?
None.
Syringe is clean. No fingerprints on it.
This means, someone wiped
the syringe clean after administering it.
Obviously the victim
couldn't wipe it after dying.
S.P. Juyal.
So someone attempted to disguise
the murder case as a drug overdose case.
Yes.
But an amateur attempt.
Ma'am.
DNA report.
Mr. Anthwal, did you handle
Aditi Tiwari's case?
Aditi Tiwari? No, I did not
investigate any such case.
By the way, who are you?
I am calling from
CICI Bank loan department.
Do you need a loan for a house,
a cycle or
It’s not Utsav Anthwal as well..
That leaves us with three now.
Madan Anthwal.
Second is Yogesh and third is Shaurya Anthwal.
How did you know it was Raghav Nautiyal?
Did the DNA reports match?
What is your link with Raghav Nautiyal?
How did you get to
the textile mill directly?
Had you read Aditi Tiwari's
post mortem report any better, you would know.
Nylon fiber and alkylphenol ethoxylates
were found in her nasal passage.
Both these products are
found in textile factories.
Clearly evident that Aditi
was held in a textile factory, Ma'am.
Away from the city in Ulaini
there's the Panchachulli textile mills,
which has been closed since 1998.
It was the perfect place to hide Aditi.
I just took my chance, Ma'am.
And how did you know that
was Raghav Nautiyal's skeleton?
Because, Ma'am, a girl a lady has kidnapped Aditi.
I was also at the
Dussehra Fair that day.
And I had seen a lady taking Aditi away.
-Why didn't you tell anyone?
-I did!
And I have been telling
people for the past 15 years.
What can I do? Nobody listens to me!
Ma'am.
DNA profile is an exact
match of Raghav Nautiyal's DNA.
Sir, his
Good job!
Good job, Juyal.
Raghav Nautiyal is the murderer.
Sanjana Tiwari had created
a commotion. F*****!
But, Sir
Sir
Sir, I think Shaurya was right.
The forensic evidence doesn't indicate
that Raghav Nautiyal could
have killed Aditi Tiwari.
How much time is left before
the statute of limitations ends?
27 hours.
A case that wasn't solved in 15 years
will be solved in 27 hours? f*****!
Let's assume it is solved.
Can you guarantee that the
Shaurya’s scandal will remain undisclosed?
This is an open and shut case.
After the kidnapping and murder,
Raghav Nautiyal died of drug overdose.
Clear case of suicide.
And I want no ifs and buts, f*****!
I want no ifs and buts!
Case
closed.
Do you get that?
Etomidate was found on the
needle used in attack, Ma'am.
It's an anesthetic and
it's not available over the counter.
It's supplied directly to hospitals.
That lady is either a resident
doctor or a nurse, Ma'am.
Our investigation is wrong.
Raghav did not kidnap her.
Even Raghav has been murdered, Ma'am!
Ma'am! You won't do anything either!
You're just like the rest of them!
We will lie again in Aditi's case?
Ma'am, Aditi deserves justice!
I have all the evidence.
We can do this
Did you send me the records
from 2001 which I’ve asked for?
Okay.
We can't sit on it.
-We have 27 hours
-Out!
- Ma'am, we have 27 hou..
- I'll do what I have to.
-We've very little time
- You let it be.
You can't do this on your own.
You need my hel
I don't need anyone's help.
Certainly not yours.
In any case, you are unworthy
of being a Police Officer.
Ma'am..please listen to me
we have only 27 hours left
Sir! Sir!
One question, Sir. Please, Sir.
Sir, tell us
Why's there so much
secrecy in the case?
Tell us the truth.
Sir, we need the truth.
Sir! Sir!
One question, Sir. Please, Sir.
We want an answer, Sir.
One question, Sir.
Did you catch Aditi's murderer?
Yes. This
I wish we had found
him alive a long time ago.
Anyway 15 years ago,
he committed suicide by drug overdose
and his body was rotting for years.
I'm sorry, Ma'am.
Ma'am
He made Raghav the culprit
and closed the case.
Truly
Ma'am.
Ma'am, please.
Get hold of yourself.
Ma'am, please. Be patient.
Bring some water.
Please bring some water for her.
I won't let this happen, Ma'am.
I will not let this happen.
Yug!
A mother received justice after 15 years.
Raghav Nautiyal was a final
year student at a medical college.
The police claim Raghav committed
suicide right after killing Aditi.
That's the reason why the
Police couldn't find him till now.
The IG personally met
and informed Sanjana Tiwari
He also expressed his condolences
Raghav did not commit the murder!
What kind of wierd statement is this?
Raghav did not commit any murder!
Raghav is innocent.
Raghav was murdered too.
The person who killed
Raghav is Aditi's killer too.
Then who killed Aditi Tiwari?
What evidence do you have for your new claims?
I am the evidence!
I found Raghav Nautiyal's skeleton
in Panchachulli textile mills.
It was a woman who
killed Raghav and Aditi.
She worked at Dehradun Medical college.
She was 20 years old at that time.
She must be 35-36 today.
-We know who you are.
-Yug!
We know who you are.
Yug Arya!
We have concrete evidence against you!
You have fooled everyone for 15 years.
-Yug Arya, stop it!
-You killed a child!
-We have concrete evidence against you!
-Stop it!
- We know who you are!
- Stop it!
-Shut up.
-Nobody can save you now!
-Be quiet, Yug!
-We know!
Turn it on. Let's watch.
Raghav did not commit murder!
Raghav is innocent.
Raghav was murdered too.
The person who killed
Raghav is Aditi's killer too.
Then who killed Aditi Tiwari?
What evidence do you have?
I am the evidence!
I found Raghav Nautiyal's skeleton
in Panchachulli textile mills.
Who is this f*****!
The crime scene was entirely staged.
To show murder as suicide.
Who is this idiot?
Have you lost your mind?
You challenged the IG himself!
Do you have any idea
what kind of mess you are in?
What is going on over here?
f*****! Who are you?
What was that nonsense outside?
I instructed him to say it.
And who gave you the authority to do that?
Are you out of your mind?
Protected the image
of the police, Sir.
And the I.G. Sir's too.
Sir.., One minute
Sir, the I.G. Sir has lied openly
If a reporter gets their hands on
the forensic report and publishes it..
I.G. Sir will instantly
be demoted then.
He did the right thing by telling the truth.
Sir, I have concrete evidence.
And a witness too.
Concrete evidence and a witness?
What evidence? What witness?
-What is he talking about, Vamika.
-Sir. Sir.
I am the witness.
I have seen the kidnapper.
Sir, it was a woman
who kidnapped Aditi Tiwari.
Approximately 5'4",
camper shoes, loose stylish clothes
wearing a cap and her face was covered, Sir.
She was probably a drug addict.
Her hands were shaking.
She was wearing a long sleeved
shirt to conceal the needle marks.
Sir, she was so deep
in debt for drugs,
she made a plan to kidnap Aditi.
She used Raghav's sim card
to send the ransom message.
When Raghav found out about
it he tried to stop his girlfriend.
His girlfriend thought
she would be exposed,
so she called Raghav to the textile mill
and attacked him with
an anesthetic syringe.
He passed out and she administered
an overdose of heroin.
She staged the crime scene
to make the murder look like suicide.
She thought the Police
would find Raghav's body
but that did not happen, Sir.
And this case remained unsolved.
And that girl is a nurse,
not a doctor, Sir.
We have evidence of that as well.
Here.
This is the October 2001 payroll
of the Government medical college.
Only two lady doctors
worked there at that time.
One was about 40 years old
and the other was on maternity leave.
Which means that the woman
we are looking for is a nurse, sir.
Both of you have lost it.
There were at least 100 nurses
at the hospital during that time.
How will you know who it was?
We don't need to talk to them all, Sir.
Everyone must have
watched the news by now.
Someone must surely know her.
It was a woman who
killed Raghav and Aditi.
She worked at Dehradun medical college.
She was 20 years old at that time.
We know who you are!
You have fooled everyone for 15 years.
You killed a child!
We know who you are!
We have concrete evidence against you!
Fuck! So much drama for one tip off!
-Did you receive any calls?
-We will.
It will take a little time
but we surely will get a call.
In the beginning nobody will believe
an acquaintance could do this.
but the nurse will panic, behave oddly,
and her colleagues will get suspicious.
We will receive the call, Sir.
Dehradun medical college!
She used to work at
-Listen
-Yes.
The woman has killed Raghav.
Did you see the news?
He is talking about
Dehradun medical college.
You worked there, didn't you?
You’ve killed a kid.
I'll be back.
We know who you are.
We have concrete evidence against you!
I said everything clearly on television
that  we have concrete evidence.
She will watch it, get scared
and behave oddly.
We will receive the call.
Pick up the fucking phone! Idiots!
All of you have turned into statues!
Police Headquarters.
Yes.
Aditi Tiwari case?
Yes. Tell me. Tell me.
Really? Okay, thank you.
Sir, the call was from Sarandeep Hospital
about Aditi Tiwari's case.
Hours
Yes, Police Headquarters
Sure, tell me the details.
Sir, we are very close to getting her.
Please let us investigate.
I take the responsibility for this.
I lead this unit and you
will take the responsibility?
Will you find the
murderer within 24 hours?
And let's say you find her.
Will you present the court
his story as evidence?
I'll make her confess, Sir.
Believe me.
Think about it, Vamika.
You will take the fall, if this fails.
Hospital
Let me
No Ma’am It's not her.
Why?
Our nurse is psychotic.
Such people are self-obsessed.
They won't care for pets.
It's not her, Ma'am. 100 percent.
Thanks.
Hello.
Jai Hind, Sir.
Head Constable Parihar here, Sir.
No, Sir. We found nothing over here.
The informant was just a prankster.
a******!
Come back.
Hey!
-Rajan! Wake up!
-Yes, Sir.
-Bring me a cup of tea.
All these f*****s just want to sleep.
Such a well-staged crime scene!
She is smart.
She can go to any lengths
to protect herself.
She is impulsive as well as nervous.
She will surely make a
mistake under pressure.
If she behaves abnormal,
then, someone will surely register too.
We know who you are!
You have been fooling everyone for 15 years,
but no more!
You have been fooling everyone for 15 years!
You killed a child!
We know who you are!
We have concrete evidence against you!
Dehradun medical college.
She worked in Dehradun medical college.
A woman killed Raghav and Aditi!
-What is her name, Sir?
-A woman!
Sir, tell us the whole story.
-Hello.
-Hello. Police Headquarters?
Yes, this is Police Headquarters.
Speak up.
I am calling from AN Hospital.
We have a nurse here. Kriti Rathudi.
Are you certain she used
to work at the medical college?
Yes, Sir.
Where is she now?
She took a shift off and
left on seeing the news.
- I see.
- She was behaving very strange.
-As in?
-I thought maybe I was overthinking.
-But then I checked her locker.
-I see.
28th October is marked.
What is this?
Narcotics Anonymous
(Missing)
(Search for missing)
(Aditi Tiwari’s dead body
was found in ganga river)
(Sanjana Tiwari announces
an indefinite Hunger Strike)
It's her! Ma'am, it's definitely her!
Where is she now?
She fled from home last night
when the news was aired.
Her credit card was swiped
in Nainital 30-35 minutes ago,
In Pine Meadows Hotel.
What's the matter?
She is in Nainital.
But SP Juyal is interfering.
He says, there's no time.
So he won't let us go and arrest her there.
Nainital is seven hours from here.
To and fro fourteen hours.
We have only seven and a half hours.
SP Juyal?
Sir, we have to request Nainital Police
to arrest Kriti Rathudi
from Pine Meadows Hotel
and airlift her here, Sir.
Have you lost your mind?
Am I the
Home Minister's son-in-law?
The news is leaked to the media, Sir.
We'll have a problem
if we don't take action.
In any case everyone feels the
I.G. office is interested in closing this case.
Really?
-Okay, I'll see what I can do.
-Okay, Sir.
What are you looking at?
Are you the only one who
can lie to get something done?
Connect me to the
Home Minister’s office.
Hotel
I do not know anyone called
Raghav Nautiyal or Aditi Tiwari.
I have only seen them on TV.
You don't know them?
Then why did you flee on seeing the news?!
I did not flee. I was right there.
Why was your phone switched off?
My phone was lost.
The moment police thrashes you,
you will speak up the truth.
I repeat. I did not flee.
Honestly. I just needed some time out.
I wanted peace.
Truly.
Minutes
It should be our dream to keep
every Indian child free from Polio.
You just have to go to nearest Polio Camp
for Polio drops to your child.
Every child has the right to live a healthy life
and it is your responsibility
to protect your child from Polio.
I went through a break up recently.
I wanted to get over it.
You don't believe me? Ask Ritu.
Ritu is my supervisor.
She will tell you all about me.
-Ritu Bhatt, right?
-Yes. Ritu Bhatt.
She will tell you everything.
She is the one who reported you.
Ritu Bhatt?
- Don’t go inside.
- Take off your shoes, Ma'am.
Ma’am, one minute
Just one minute.
- Please, Ma'am. Just one minute.
- Balwant stop!
Take off your shoe.
Take them off.
-Hurry!
-I'm on it.
Let's see you walk.
Hurry!
Walk! Walk!
She is not the suspect
we are looking for.
Much ado about nothing, Ma'am.
The shoes I mistook for camper
shoes were actually special shoes
that patients with mild polio
wears to hide the limp
Our nurse has polio.
She has Polio
Look at this.
Look!
Is this your locker?
Not Mine..
This is Ritu Bhatt's locker.
Ritu Bhatt's locker.
You are rushing for no need.
She must have fled.
She did not flee the city
even after committing double murder.
When the news came
out that the case is opened
she shifted the blame
on Kriti instead of fleeing.
She deceived the Police and caused delay.
Why is she doing this?
She is taking a risk.
She is enjoying the game. Like drugs.
She derives a bigger kick
the closer she is to the mess.
It means that she is right here.
Play the feed of the
Headquarters' surroundings. Hurry.
Ma'am, please.
Do as he says.
Alright Ma’am.
There she is!
Camera one.
The one with the red umbrella.
Sir! Sir!
-Sir, answer us!
- Let me go
We want an answer!
Answer us! We want an answer!
Who is going to take responsibility
for turning the country's law into a joke?
Is the Police ready to do anything
to close the case?
You didn't find the culprit,
so you arrested an innocent person?
Speak up!
-Move aside.
-Speak up!
-Move
-Tell us the truth, Inspector! Speak up!
Speak up!
Sir! Sir!
Sir! Tell us the truth!
Did you find Ritu Bhatt's
car registration number?
Message me.
Speak up!
I said, Move.
Let me go.
Closed